A lot of y'all think I'm living the
dream, but right now it feels like the
nightmare. Sunday, May 3rd, my father,
Mike Fells, passed away after a year's
long battle with Parkinson's disease.
He took it like a champ. He never once
complained. He never asked for pity or
sympathy. He never once said, "Why me?"
He was the most influential man in my
life.
He put the love of God in my heart and
the knowledge of Jesus in my mind at a
young age. He read the Bible to me every
day. Every morning we had a prayer hike
as a family. Every night we had prayer
time as a family. He had me in church
three times a week. He delivered me when
he was a missionary in Papua New Guinea
with his own two hands. My dad taught me
so many things. He was a runner, a
marathoner, and he always told me to
catch him on the hill, son. And with
those words echoing in my mind, I've run
mountains. With the knowledge of Jesus
he put in my head, I built the Jesus
house. And with the love of God he put
in my heart, I've been building the
Fells House database. I really wanted
him to see it complete so he could see
the fruit bearing forth in my life from
the seed that he planted, but it'll
never happen cuz he's gone. We were so
close to having this database up, but it
didn't get it done in time, and I'll
feel forever guilty for not having it
done so my dad could see it. Almost
18,000 pages scanned. We have multiple
uploaded. We have 23 books in here right
now. I just wanted to come on here and
tell y'all how I got to this place in my
life and why I do these strange things
that I do. It was my dad, and he's gone,
and I don't know really how to handle
it. And I'm going to dedicate this site
to him.
Mike Fells.
He was a good man. There's not many left
in this earth. He was an honest man, and
he spent his life helping people and
giving back. But he went with dignity,
and he went with grace, and he laid me a
path forward. Till next week when we
roll this site out and you log in, I
want you to say a little prayer and give
thanks for Mike Fells cuz he's the
reason you're going to read these things
online. I'm going to get this thing up
and live, and I just wanted to tell you
where it's coming from and why it's
happening.
I miss my dad.
>> [snorts]